Kettle Title
What does this mean? It's my first time.
I wonder what it is.
It's easy to understand.
I see.
It all shows on my face.
It shows on my face.
If I like something, I like it a lot.
If I'm not interested, I'm not interested.
I think about it a lot.
If I don't like something on Instagram...
If I didn't really like something
I don't like it.
That's right.
It's not like that, right?
I see.
If I didn't think it was cute...
If I didn't think it was cute, I wouldn't have said it was cute.
That's true.
It's true.
I'm definitely in my own mind.
That's right, isn't it?
You can't lose, can you?
Honestly
Have you ever had the privilege of being honest with yourself?
Have you?
I don't get tired.
I see.
What's that?
It's important
It's very important to fit in.
But by going my own way.
I feel like I can preserve who I am.
So...
Frustration, yes or no.
Is there anything else?
Like I said, I don't...
I don't say pretty very often.
I don't say pretty to people.
I don't.
But now that my sisters have five younger members.
They're the five younger members.
They're cute.
It's hard to say.
It's a natural outpouring of self-initiative.
Honest Ms. Nakayama is here.
I've come to come out.
I see.
You think you're cute from the bottom of your heart.
That's the first time I've ever felt that way.
It's the first time I've ever felt that way.
It's like having a sister.
That's very honest.
I mean...
I hate April Fool's Day.
I don't do anything.
I'm not going to do anything.
I'm not going to do it.
What's the custom?
People do it all the time.
There's no such thing as a happy lie.
I'm being honest.
It's just a normal day.
So it's true.
Because it's April Fool's Day?
Fujii...
Let's do it as an appetizer.
I don't think so.
I wonder if he's taking care of Ms. Nakayama.
I'm making her feel sorry for me.
No.
Surprise for someone.
Surprise?
Surprises? Surprises?
In my mind.
That's not a good idea.
I mean, it's not bad.
I don't set things up.
I don't do that.
Then tell your brother.
Then surprise him.
Surprise him.
I can't hide it.
It shows on my face.
I can't do that.
I'm often asked...
"Of all the things I do in this job, I love live performances the most.
I really like it.
The way you look...
There are no expectations.
They are really enjoying themselves to the fullest
That's what I like about it.
I've had so many people tell me how great it is.
I've had so many people tell me how great I am.
So, on the other hand...
On the other hand...
Of course I have this job in acting, but...
But stage?
Is it more like drama?I guess it's more like that than a drama or something.
Stage
I see.
I want to be in the moment.
Me.
As entertainment.
I want people to see me expressing myself.
I love the stage.
It is a hobby consistently
I think it's the most important thing
Mr. Nakayama
Surprise me.
I'd like to do something like that.
I'd like to do that.
I'd like to try it, but I'd probably get turned down.
I'd tell her... but I don't think I could.
I think you've given me the most honest feedback.
Thank you very much.
This program is...
Mr. Rico.
Mr. Richimasa
Mr. Roneko
Mr. Massa
This program was provided by Keisuke RinaHinariKoushi
Thank you very much!